<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="help_add_card">
        Click on the plus icon to create a conversion card
    </string>

    <string name="help_card_update_label">
        The card update label displays the last time the conversion price was updated
    </string>

    <string name="help_card_delete_button">
        Click on the delete button of a card to delete that conversion card
    </string>

    <string name="help_card_sync_button">
        The sync button fetches the current conversion price between the cryptocurrency and the
        base currency
    </string>

    <string name="help_conversion_symbol">
        It shows the short code for the cryptocurrency, the currency code for the base currency
        and also a flag to identify the country that uses that base currency. Like in the image above
        it displays BTC(Bitcoin) and NGN(Nigerian Naira) with the Nigerian Flag
    </string>

    <string name="help_conversion_price">
        This displays the price of the cryptocurrency in base currency. Like in the image above, it
        shows that 1 bitcoin costs 2,601,653,72 Nigerian Naira
    </string>

    <string name="help_start_conversion">
        To start conversion click on the conversion card. This would be anywhere else besides the
        buttons
    </string>

    <string name="help_card_created">
        The card created view box displays the date and time in which the conversion card was created
    </string>

    <string name="help_card_updated_details">
        This box displays exactly the same date as that in the previous screen. Only this time
        it shows it in a more human friendly form
    </string>

    <string name="help_convert">
        the convert card displays the price of one crypto currency in the corresponding base
        currency and it has two input fields(one for the cryptocurrency value and the other for
        the base currency value). The conversion is done in both directions and results are obtained
        on the go i.e as values change in the field
    </string>

    <string name="help_synchronise">
        Performs the same function as the sync button on the conversion card
    </string>

    <string name="help_crypto_icon">
        An icon that represents the cryptocurrency
    </string>
</resources>